goinflow.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 26, 2018. This document governs the privacy policy of our websites[ www.goinflow.com](https://www.goinflow.com/) and[ www.inflowconversion.com](https://www.inflowconversion.com/). We know that privacy and confidentiality are important to our subscribers and clients.

### **Information We Collect**

We collect personally identifiable information when you fill out any of our website forms in order to access content, contact us about our services, or subscribe to our email newsletter. This information includes the following categories:

  1. Personal contact information
  2. Interest Categories
  3. Industry information
  4. Company information

This information is voluntarily provided when you fill out our forms and you control the amount and type of information provided when visiting our websites. As a visitor, you can browse our website without providing any information, it is not a requirement.

### **How Information is Used**

How your information is used depends on the forms that you fill out. We use email addresses to contact you about our services, provide additional content relating to our services, maintain client communications, and send email newsletters. These email addresses are only for agency use and are never shared with unaffiliated outside parties without your permission.

Information gathered through cookies and Google Analytics tracking does not contain personally identifying information and its use is limited to providing and improving our websites. 

We never use or share any personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to those described above without providing you the opportunity to opt-out or prohibit such uses. 

### **Communication**

When we communicate with you, we will use only the email address you provide to us through form submissions. Email communications can include: newsletters, content offers with download links, and promotional information about our services. 

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can opt-out of these emails at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our emails. You can also update your information by sending a message to [Marketing@Goinflow.com](mailto:Marketing@Goinflow.com).

### **Cookies and Tracking**

Our websites use “cookies” (small pieces of data stored on your computer or mobile devices by your web browser). Cookies are used to identify the areas of our websites that you visit. These cookies are also used to improve your browsing experience by eliminating the need to submit multiple forms in order to access certain pieces of content. In some cases, cookies may be used to personalize the content you see on our website. Most web browsers allow users the option to disable the use of cookies, if this is information that you do not want to share with us.

Additionally, information such as your IP address, browser type, language, and the date and time of your requests may be automatically recorded. We use this information to track trends amongst users in order to improve your experience. 

### **Google Ad Content and Google Analytics**

Our websites use Google Analytics to collect information about users on our site. Google Analytics tracks how often users visit, the pages being visited, browsing behavior, referring sites, and so forth. We use this information in order to improve our site. While Google Analytics records the IP address assigned to you on the date that you visit our site, Google Analytics does not track any identifying information. You can learn more about Google Analytics by reading the[ Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html). 

### **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Inflow reserves the right to change and update our privacy policy at any time. Updates will always be posted to this page. If our policy should change in a manner that might result in the disclosure of personally identifiable information that a visitor or client has provided, we will contact you via email in order to provide you the opportunity to prevent such disclosure.

If you have any questions about this policy, please reach out via the contact information at the top of the page.
